Vikas Sharma

<u>vikasraajoriya@gmail.com</u> • +91 895-596-1947 <u>https://www.linkedin.com/in/th3g3ntl3m3n</u> • <u>https://github.com/th3g3ntl3m3n</u>

Summary

Full Stack Engineer with 5 years of experience. Always learning new technologies and good computer science fundamentals. Good team member and give priority to humanity.

Skills

Go • React • React native • PostgreSQL • Rest API • DevOps • Python • Flutter

Work Experience

Full Stack DeveloperJun 2018 – present

Contract • Contract

Remote

Technologies: Golang • React • React native • PostgreSQL • Rest API

- Designed and Developed **SaaS** based **Route Planning system.** System allow clients to optimally route their assets for given arrival time and provide real time tracking and traffic aware eta time of assets.
- Designed **inhouse custom routing automation algorithm** which efficiently route the assets and **eliminate 70% of manual routing work**.
- System also lessen the burden of big Speadsheet to maintain assets and routing for clients as they can use **customisable reporting** provided by system.

Full Stack JavaScript AND Mobile Application Developer

Mar 2017 - Jun 2018 • 1 yr 3 mos

Hawkscode Software • Full-time

Jaipur, India

Technologies: Node.js • React • React native • PostgreSQL • Rest API

- Contributed in various project with different technologies.
- Developed hybrid mobile applications in ReactNative.
- Developed full stack applications with Nodejs, Reactjs in various business domains. e.g. Gym, Transportation.
- Provided training to interns in company in mobile and frontend technologies.

Salesforce Developer

Sep 2016 – Dec 2016 • 3 mos

ConcretIO Apps • Internship

Jaipur, India

Technologies: Salesforce

- Learnt Salesforce Admin platform.
- Learnt Salesforce Developer platform and Apex, Lightning Pages, Aura, Triggers, Custom Objects, SOQL.
- Worked on enhancement tasks of running projects.

Educations

Bachelor's degree: Computer Science & Engineering

Aug 2012 - May 2016 • 3 yrs 9 mos

Poornima College Of Engineering

Jaipur, India

Languages

English (Professional working proficiency)